(Zack:)Penny?
Oh. Zack, hi!
(Penny:)You guys remember Zack.
(Howard:)Yeah, hey, buddy.
- Hello. - Hey.
(Zack:)Hey, did you two
get married?
(Penny:)We did.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
(Zack:)To each other?
Yes. (chuckles)
Cool. 'Cause other than
when you broke up with him
(Zack:)and dated me, then
broke up with me,
(Zack:)and then dated me one more
time before going back to him,
(Zack:)I was always rooting
for you two.
(Raj:)Thanks.
(Zack:)So how's the
science world?
(Penny:)What are you
guys up to?
W-We've actually been
working on a prototype
(Howard:)for a navigation
system we invented.
(Leonard:)But we won't bore you
with the details.
(Zack:)Are you kidding?
I love science.
(Zack:)Einstein, Stephen Hawking,
Mike deGrasse Tyson.
(Amy:)Mike deGrasse Tyson?
(Howard:)Yeah, you know,
the boxer who grew a mustache
(Howard:)and became a scientist.
(Zack:)So what's your
invention?
(Howard:)Well, we're using
quantum vortices
(Howard:)to replace gyroscopes
in guidance systems.
(Leonard:)What's neat is
that they can maintain
(Leonard:)angular momentum indefinitely.
(Leonard:)Angular momentum.